Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - Ibo music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C90; C83/310 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR331)
    Nigeria. Contents: Music. People/language group: Ibo. Original field recording.
  - Ibo music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C90; C83/311 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR332)
  - Hausa music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/312 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR333)
    Nigeria. Contents: Music. People/language group: Hausa. Original field recording.
  - Berik music, ca. 1974, 1 sound cassette; C74/313 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR334)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Berik tribes, North Coast of Irian Jaya, Indonesia, analysis data used at Wheaton. SIL - Westrum (duplicate). Berik Songs sung by old man, Somanente. Music. Collected by Sue and Peter Westrum. People/language group: Berik. Duplicate of field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1983-07-21, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/314 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR335)
    Papua New Guinea. Contents: Side A. Bougainville, Roreinang village, Nasioi language. July 21, 1983. Side B. Bougainville, Parina village. Music. July 27, 1983. Collected by D. Clouse and R. Colgren. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - West Sepik Province music, 1983-06, 1 sound cassette, C90; C83/315 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR336)
    Papua New Guinea. West Sepik. Contents: Kambirap and Panenkin village songs. Recorded June 16th, 1983. Tape #1. Auya II Village Sing-Sing and songs. June 19, 1983. Music. Recorded by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Karkar. Original field recording.
  - West Sepik Province music, 1983-06-16, 1 sound cassette, C90; C83/316 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR337)
    Papua New Guinea. West Sepik. Contents: Tape 1. Trowari Village. June 16th, 1983. Tree Cutting [Auya village] Kambrirap village songs [Farino]. Music. Recorded by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Karkar.
  - West Sepik Province music, 1983-06-19, 1 sound cassette, C90; C83/317 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR338)
    Papua New Guinea. West Sepik. Contents: Auya II Village. June 19th, 1983. Music. Collected by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse.
  - Nasioi songs, 1983-07-25, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/318 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR339)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Nasioi songs (Bougainville). Music. Collected by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Nasioi and Siwai.
  - North Solomons music, 1983-07, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/319 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR340)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Siwai (cont.), Holia, Haku. Tape #2. Kunua and Haku. Tape #2. Dubbed July 26, 1983. Music. Collected by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Nasioi and Siwai.
  - Bougainville and Buka Island music collection, 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/320 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR341)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Tape #3 of music collection Bougainville and Buka Island. Music. Collected by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Halia, Teop, and Nagovisi.
  - North Solomons music collection, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/321 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR342)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Tape #4 of North Solomons music collection. Music. Collected by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Solos, Rotokas, and Tinputz.
  - North Solomons music collection, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/322 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR343)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Tape #5 of North Solomons music collection. Nissan cont. Music. Collected by Claire Bureau and Duane Clouse. People/language group: Tinputz and Teop.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1982, 1 sound tape reel; R82/323 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR344)
    Special call number: .5986 Pli. Dubbing from an earlier recording.
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R /324 (no year) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR345)
  - Music from Hawaii, Maori, Tahiti, Marquesas, Samoa, Tongo, Fiji, 1977, 1 sound cassette; C77/325 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR346)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/326 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR347)
  - Hawaiian song and dance, 1977, 1 sound cassette; C77/327 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR348)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1957, 1 sound tape reel; R57/328 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR349)
  - Music from Tahiti, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette, C60; C80/329 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR350)
  - Music from Tahiti, ca. 1977, 1 sound cassette, C60; C77/330 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR351)
    French Polynesia. Tahiti. Contents: Bonruée Tenete. Music. Collected by unnamed friend of Stephen and Janice Schooling.
  - Arabic music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/331 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR352)
    Contents: Sounds of the Arab World. Music.
  - latmul music of Papua New Guinea, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/332 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR353)
    Papua New Guinea. East Sepik Province. Contents: Music of Oceania. The latmul of Papua New Guinea. Music. People/language group: Iatmul. Dubbed from commercial LP "Music of Oceania: Papua Niugini: The Middle Sepik" (Institute for Musicology of the University of Basle).
  - latmul music of Papua New Guinea, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/333 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR354)
    Papua New Guinea. East Sepik Province. Contents: Music of Oceana. Middle Sepik Region. Music. People/language group: Iatmul. Dubbed from commercial LP "Music of Oceania: Papua Niugini: The Middle Sepik" (Institute for Musicology of the University of Basle).
  - Kofare Songs, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette, C60; C82/334 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR355)
    Papua New Guinea. Oro Province. Contents: Kofare Songs from Tufi, Northern Province, Papua New Guinea. Music. Collected by Jim and Cindy Farr. People/language group: Korafe.
  - Music from Vietnam, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette; C82/335 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR356)
    Vietnam. Contents: Music. Collected by Tai Dam. Dubbed from stereo commercial disc by Wheaton student Shirley Huang.
  - Music from Solomon Islands, Papua New Guinea and Cook Islands, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/336 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR357)
    Solomon Islands, Papua New Guinea and Cook Islands. Contents: (SI) Mortlock (SI) Santa Isabel, Gulf Province (SI) bamboo band. Music. Collected by Vida Chenoweth.
  - South Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette, C90; C80/337 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR358)
    Papua New Guinea. Port Moresby. Contents: S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby, 1980. Tape 7. Music. Collected by Vida Chenoweth.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/338 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR359)
  - Aborigines in Arakun and Queensland, 1967, 1 sound cassette; C67/339 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR360)
  - Dani music, 1983-06, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/340 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR361)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Dani Hymns. Dani Traditional songs. Music. Collected by Duane Clouse. People/language group: Dani.
  - Nigerian music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/341 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR362)
    Nigeria. Contents: Zabiya and her group from Takum, Gongola State. Madi mai Molo and his groups from Maiduguri, Borno State, Nigeria. Music. People/language group: Hausa. Dubbed from previous recording.
  - Nigerian music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/342 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR363)
    Nigeria. Contents: Peter Bambo - Hausa From Jos Plateau State, Nigeria. Mukadas Dan Mai Awo From Saminaka, Kaduna State, Nigeria. Music. People/language group: Hausa. Dubbed from previous recording.
  - Nigerian music, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/343 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR364)
    Nigeria. Contents: Women's Fellowship. Kagoro, Kaduna State, Nigeria. Women's Fellowship. Jos, Plateau State, Nigeria. Music. Dubbed by Joseph Gamu. People/language group: Hausa. Dubbed from previous recording.
  - Maure music, ca. 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/344 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR365)
    Senegal. Mbane. Contents: Side A. Sounds - Singing and Dancing. Side B. Preacher Coming One World Religon. Music. Collected by Jenny Carpender and Barbara Scott. People/language group: Maure.
  - Buluchi music, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette, C60; C80/345 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR366)
    Contents: Buluchi Music, Azzam. Music. Collected by Robert Bailey.
  - Kiribas music, 1981-06-24, 1 sound cassette, C60; C81/346 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR367)
    Solomon Islands. Kiribas. Contents: Music of Kiribas. Rec. at Honiara.
  - Maori Greeting, 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/347 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR368)
    Contents: Maori Greeting to the Prince and Princess of Wales, Gisborn.
  - Karkar interview, 1983-06-17, 1 sound cassette, C90; C83/348 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR369)
    Papua New Guinea. West Sepik. Contents: Informant Session #1. Informant Session #2. Spoken word/interview. Collected by Collected by Claire Bureau. People/language group: Karkar.
  - Tai music, undated, 1 sound cassette; C83/349 (no year) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR370)
    Thailand. Contents: Music. People/language group: Tai. Second generation recording.
  - Cambodian instrumental music from commercial recording, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette; C83/350 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR371)
    Cambodia. Contents: Instrumental Music duplicate from commercial. Collected by Pastor Reach.
  - Tai Dam music, ca. 1978, 1 sound cassette, C60; C78/351 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR372)
    Vietnam. Contents: Tai Dam Music. Recorded in Des Moines Iowa by Bacum Hung. Language study Tai Dam. Dubbed off WHO by Dan Lim Keman. Music. Collected by Jim Brase with linguist Jay Flippinger and Tai Dam leader [Bakhoa Hung]. People/language group: Tai Dam. C81/354 is also in LOC 040.01e.
  - Tai Dam music, 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/352 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR373)
    Vietnam. Contents: Tai Dam Music. Rec. Jim Brase, Iowa. Songs 1-4. Songs 4 -9. Music. Collected by Jim Brase. People/language group: Tai Dam. C80/352 is also in LOC 040.01b.
  - Tai Dam music, 1969-1974, 1 sound cassette; C69/353 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR374)
    Vietnam. Contents: Tai Dam Music. Recorded in South Vietnam by Jay Flippenger. Songs 10-16. Dubbed by Dan Limekeman. 1981. Wito. Music. Collected by Jay Flippinger, dubbed by Dan Limkeman. People/language group: Tai Dam. Dubbed from field recordings by Jay Flippinger. C69/353 is also contained in LOC 040.01a.
  - Tai Dam music, 1981-06-28, 1 sound cassette; C81/354 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR375)
    Vietnam. Contents: Tai Dam Music. Recorded in Oskaloosa, IA by Jay Flippinger, June 28, 1981. Songs #17-24. #17-24 = 01-08 on tape. Music. Collected by Jay Flippinger. People/language group: Tai Dam.
  - Tai Dam music, 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/355 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR376)
    Vietnam. Contents: Tai Dam Music. Recorded in Oskaloosa, UA. Songs 30-35. Tai Dam Songs 036-039. Music. Collected by Dan Limkeman. People/language group: Tai Dam. See also LOC 040.01f.
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R /356 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR377)
    Collected by Kathleen Barker.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/357 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR378)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/358 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR379)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound cassette; R68/358 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR380)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/359 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR381)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/360 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR382)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/361 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR383)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/362 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR384)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/363 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR385)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R68/364 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR386)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/365 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR387)
  - Usarufa, ca. 1967, 1 sound cassette; R67/366 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR388)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1983, 1 sound tape reel; R83/367 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR389)
  - Serer songs, ca. 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/368 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR390)
  - Cambodian music in Thailand, 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/369 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR391)
    Cambodia. Contents: Cambodian music at refugee camp in Thailand. Duplicate, tape 1. Music. Recorded by Pastor Yea Reach. Duplicate from field recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/370 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR392)
  - Berik music, 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/371 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR393)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/372 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR394)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/373 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR395)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/374 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR396)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/375 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR397)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/376 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR398)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/377 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR399)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/378 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR400)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/379 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR401)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/380 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR402)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/381 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR403)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel; R69/382 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR404)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel; R65/383a (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR405)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel; R65/383b (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR406)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/384 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR407)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1962, 1 sound tape reel; R62/385 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR408)
    Collected by Darlene Bee.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1962, 1 sound tape reel; R62/386 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR409)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1972, 1 sound tape reel; R72/387 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR410)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound cassette; R/65/388 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR411)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/389 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR412)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/390 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR413)
  - Old songs, Aayurabaqa, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/391 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR414)
    Contents: Old songs, fight, initiation, memory. Girls, women, Aayurabaqa. Collected by Vida Chenoweth.
  - Aayurabaqa, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/392 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR415)
    Contents: Sweat-house. Aayurabaqa. Collected by Vida Chenoweth.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/393 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR416)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/394 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR417)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/395 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR418)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1971, 1 sound tape reel; R71/396 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR419)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/397 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR420)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/398 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR421)
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/399 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR422)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: South Nasioi area, Kairena Village Sing-Sing. Tape II. Side A. Original. Music. Collected by Harold Wilkin and Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/400 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR423)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: South Nasioi area, Roreinang Village. Tape 7. Side A. Rotakas area, Togarao District, Togarao Village. Tape 7. Side B. Music. Collected by Harold Wilkin. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-07, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/401 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR424)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: South Nasioi area, Kairena Village. Sing-sing. Tape 8. Side A. Music. Collected by Harold Wilkin. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-07, 1 sound cassette; C84/402 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR425)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Kairina village, Nasioi Language. All night Sing-Sing, 1st tape. Original. Music. Collected by Timothy Cooley. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-07, 1 sound cassette; C84/403 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR426)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Kairina village, Nasioi Language. All night Sing-Sing, 2nd tape. Original. Music. Collected by Timothy Cooley. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-28, 1 sound cassette, C60; C84/404 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR427)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: Roreinang. Papua New Guinea. Moses Karena. Mesgach Tarurara. Harold Wilkin Wheaton College, Wheaton, IL, USA. Music. Collected by Harold Wilkin. People/language group: Nasioi, Rotokas. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-07, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/405 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR428)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: South Nasioi language. Roreinang. Kairena Village. Tape 9. Kairena Village Sing-Sing. Original. Music. Collected by Harold Wilkin and Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-07, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/406 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR429)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: South Nasioi language. Roreinang. Kairena Village. Tape 10. Kairena Village Sing-Sing. Original. Music. Collected by Harold Wilkin and Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-07-02, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/407 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR430)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomon Islands. Contents: South Nasioi area, Roreinang Village, Tok Ples Skul. Traditional style. Tape 6. Collected by: Harold Wilkin. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Nasioi music, 1984-06-28, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/408 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR431)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons Island. Contents: Rotokas area, Wakunai District, Kaukoro Village. Tape 3. Side B: Kieta District, SIL Centre, Second Rotokas Analysis Check. Check Performed by Amos Tevaria from Tongarau District of Rotokas. Music. Collected by: Harold Wilkin. People/language group: Nasioi. Original field recording.
  - Buin music, 1984-07, 1 sound cassette; C84/409 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR432)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons Island. Contents: Kikimogo Village. Buin Language area. Music. Collected by: Margie Griffin. People/language group: Buin. Original field recording.
  - Buin music, ca. 1984, 1 sound cassette, C60; C84/410 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR433)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons Province. Contents: Buyin Area, Kukumai Village. Jennifer Runner, student of Dr. Vida Chenoweth of Wheaton College, Wheaton, IL. Music. Collected by: Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Buin. Original field recording.
  - Buin music, 1984, 1 sound cassette; C84/411 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR434)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons Province. Contents: Tietuno village; Uisai language area. Maramuukuu Village; Buin language area. June-July, 1984. Music. Collected by: Jack Pankinu. People/language group: Uisai. Original field recording.
  - Buin music, 1984-07-24, 1 sound cassette, C60; C84/412 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR435)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Buin, Marapita Village. Singer: Francis Baubake. Music. Collected by: Jack Pankinu. People/language group: Buin. Original field recording.
  - Buin music, 1984-07, 1 sound cassette; C84/413 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR436)
    Papua New Guinea; North Solomons Province Buin and Tokumouguu Villages. Buin Language area. Tokumouguu, Pamoiuuto, and Kikimogo village. Collected by Jedd Meyer and Margie Griffin. People/language group: Buin. Original field recording.
  - Usarufa music, 1984-06-22, 1 sound cassette; C84/414 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR437)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Kaarité village. Contents: Side A. Sing-sing for video. Side B. Sacred flutes. Komaatamá's (luluai) pattern. Music. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Usarufa music, 1984-06-23, 1 sound cassette; C84/415 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR438)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Contents: Umínánúbáqá hamlet. Tape 2, Side A. Iqarénabe's songs (cont.) #27-#3. Music. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Usarufa music, 1984-06-23, 1 sound cassette; C84/416 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR439)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Contents: Umínánúbáqá hamlet. Tape 1, Side A. Iqarénabe's song #1-#13. Umínánúbáqá hamlet. Tape 1, Side B. Iqarénabe's songs (cont.) #14-#26. Music. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Nagovisi music, 1984-06-09, 1 sound cassette; C84/417 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR440)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Siandaro Village. Contents: Nagovisi language area. Music. People/language group: Nagovisi. Original field recording.
  - Uisai music, 1984-06-23, 1 sound cassette; C84/418 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR441)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Sulekunu #2 and Horemai villages. Side A. June 23-24, 1984. Horemai and Teituno Villages. Side B. June 24-25, 1984. Music. Collected by Jack Pankinu. People/language group: Uisai. Original field recording.
  - Uisai music, 1984-06-21, 1 sound cassette; C84/419 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR442)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Koukousino and Kekemono villages. Side A. June 21, 1984. Ulekunu #1, Koohui, and Sulekunu #2 villages, Uisai language area. Side B. June 22-23, 1984. Music. Collected by Jeff Meyer and Jack Pankinu. People/language group: Uisai. Original field recording.
  - Teop-Tinputz music, 1984-07-02, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/420 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR443)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Teop-Tinputz, Takani Village. Music. Collected by Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Teop/Tinputz. Original field recording.
  - Teop-Tinputz music, 1984-07-03, 1 sound cassette, C60; C84/421 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR444)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Teop-Tinputz, Suri, Namatoa, and Hantobin Villages. Music. Collected by Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Teop/Tinputz. Original field recording.
  - Teop-Tinputz music, 1984-06-28, 1 sound cassette, C60; C84/422 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR445)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Teop checking session. Wheaton College, Wheaton, IL. Music. Collected by Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Teop/Tinputz. Original field recording.
  - Teop-Tinputz music, 1984-06-29, 1 sound cassette, C60; C84/423 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR446)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Teop-Tinputz, Teop Island. Wheaton College, Wheaton, IL. Music. Collected by Jennifer Runner. People/language group: Teop/Tinputz. Original field recording.
  - Kieta sounds, 1984-07, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/424 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR447)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: P. Kieta, sounds of early morning. Music. People/language group: Kieta. Original field recording.
  - Port Moresby Solomon Islands Night by university students, 1984-06-03, 1 sound cassette, C90; C84/425 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR448)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Port Moresby Solomon Islands Night by university students. Side A 000-260. Music. Original field recording.